SHAILESH RAMESH MARU

(+91) 8082418309 (+91 7303660981) • Mumbai, India • Shaileshmaru70@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Professional with over 5 years of experience in management. Five years of Administration and Auditing. Possess strong analytical, leadership and communication skills. Able to meet and exceed goals in any environment.

Areas of Expertise

MS Office Vendor Management Housekeeping Management Office Management Business Administration Strategic Planning Records Management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HGS International Services Private Limited, Mumbai, India

Internal Auditor & Administrative Manager in **DBS Bank**, July 2017 - December 2018 Key Responsibilities for Audit

- Undertake audit projects to provide reliable and independent assurance.
- Identify and assess potential risks in accordance with current regulatory and statutory requirements.
- Establish and build relationships with senior stakeholders to educate the business in the control framework and influence business processes.
- Define and develop Continuous Auditing requirements.

Key Responsibilities for Administrative

- Responsible for all matters related to administration.
- Maintain Fixed Asset Register.
- Maintaining documents, billing coordination with accounts, details of all cancellation and change in dates
- Maintaining stock and providing stationary within Audit Premises
- Arranging all Audit events
- Managing office supplies, pantry supplies and refreshments regularly
- Arranging for visa, tickets & travel accommodation
- Vendor management

ITM GROUP OF INSTITUTES. NERUL, MUMBAI.

Academic Coordinator from March-17 till June-2017

Duties & Responsibilities: -

- Assists the Central General Registrar with daily office responsibilities.
- Making Consolidated Centralized MIS report (on roll Students, Fees, staff, exam & placement details)
- Assists staff in resolving complex residency, admissions and registration issues.
- Issue transcript marks sheet and degree certificate.
- Compiles training materials for a new staff member.
- Submits and maintains files in a storage facility.
- Verifies enrollment for all students to include eligibility criteria.
- Submits and maintains campus wise discrepancy list.
- Plans and directs the campus wise internal audit program; conduct internal audits; examines financial aid records, procedures, operational and accounting systems of the ITM Group.
- Establishes policies for the auditing activity and directs its technical and administrative functions;
 maintains audit procedure manuals.
- Develops and executes a comprehensive audit program to evaluate management controls overall financial activities.
- Reviews all reports of examination and related working audit.
- Prepares Half yearly audit schedule of the Internal Audit Department.
- Performs other duties as assigned.

ALTFORT CAPITAL ADVISORS PVT LTD. NARIMAN POINT, MUMBAI

Assistant Manager Administration, March 16 - Nov-16

Responsible for all matters related to the Operations and Administration.

ENRICH SKIN & HAIR SOLUTION PVT LTD. MUMBAI.

Salon Executive from Aug 2015 - Feb 2016.

Duties & Responsibilities: -

- Managing client appointments.
- Keep up with the demand of clients. Managing salon personnel.
- Setting targets for beauty therapists.
- Managing, motivating and training a small team of Stylists. Resolving guest complaints or issues.
- Managing and forecasting retail stock levels.
- Organizing promotion and marketing campaigns.
- Ensuring high standards of hygiene, cleanliness within the salon.
- Identifying staff training requirements.
- Analyzing weekly and monthly sales figures. Controlling salon expenses.

SITA INFOBYTES SOLUTION PRIVATE LTD. GOVANDI, MUMBAI.

As "Back office Executive" later Promoted to "General Manager" from June 2012 to July 2013.

Duties & Responsibilities: -

- Calling Existing Customer, Cold Calling New Customer for Promotion and sales of products.
- Data Entry in company Website.
- Preparing Quotations, Invoices and Purchase Order for the existing products and services.
- Contacting the new publisher and arranging for sales.

General Manager: -

- Leading and directing employees.
- Manage Staff & preparing work schedules.
- Assigning specific duties.
- Overseeing all administrative functions & Increasing management effectiveness by hiring and training new employees.
- Weekly meeting to discuss specific roles and duties.

PAREKH SHAH & LODHA (BKC ADVISORS). ANDHERI, MUMBAI

As a Junior Auditor (Trainee) from Jan 2011 to May 2012.

EDUCATION

- (PGDFM) Post Graduation Diploma in Finance Management, Mumbai University, Maharashtra, NH April 2017
- (B.Com) Bachelor of Commerce, Mumbai University, Maharashtra, IN May 2015

DECLARATION

I hereby declare the information given is correct to the best of my knowledge & belief. I understand that any wrong information makes me liable for dismissal forthwith.

Shailesh Maru